Looks like it's hanging
Yeah, did you see that
So how do you move it
We're going to switch to his chassis motion right now
Uh, it's forward
This is back
The chassis can also go back and forth
Yeah, and then this is a shift to the left
Oh oh
It also supports rotating in place
Oh
Well, I don't think it's that much trouble
If I'm a good driver
I don't need this.
Why don't we have a game or something
Well.
Actually came to our scene today
How do you compete
How do you compete in your field
It's just a lateral shift
You are familiar with
It's just two cars parked here
Leave a space for another car
Um, can we just time it
Whoa, slow down
Oh, my gosh
Whoops whoops
Lose money, lose money
Oh boy
Insurance. Insurance company. Oops
This kid never got his driver's license
We're going to switch the vehicle from normal to parking
and then we're going to put the Mcnamum wheel down
Turn in place first
It's much steadier
It's steady
It's a second kill. Haha
hawa
Model car team
I wonder if you were working with them on purpose
It's hard, isn't it
Reverse into the garage
We looked at a traditional reverse mode
and a new way to perform a PK
It has nothing to do with the technology of their operation
It just has to do with the laws of physics
Because when you pulled over
You have a four-wheel design like this
When you need to park
You need to park it
He must have space