Teen Science Dream Show
Young Edison Minhang Division final
starts at Xinzhuang Town Sports Center
5 groups of science kids with their own scientific works
are live judged by 4 experts
and the jury
An elbow-opening lock aid
melanin spot detection
automotive shifters, automatic color toners
bicycle riding alarm device
Five groups of students showed their ideas
Questions from the mentor group
also increased the creative research and judgment
On and off the field
All felt the impact of thinking from science
Chenyu Zhou from the 2nd affiliated High School of ECNU
won the junior Edison championship in Minhang
Shanghai Xinzhuang Senior High School
Shanghai Star River Bay Bilingual School, etc
won the Best Human Support award
Best scientific Potential award
Best Market Value Award
and Best Contribution to Life award respectively
We can open our minds
through this game
Through our minds
to solve some problems in your life
I think that's the key
This is a kind of affirmation
of our efforts and efforts for so long
It will power some of our future research
Let's do better
This is really a lot of happiness
Science dream mentor Yuan Ming
was also moved by
and technological innovation works
She told reporters
after the event
These children can use their eyes,
with their knowledge,
with their spirit of never giving up,
to make this possible step by step into reality
These players,
the kind of acumen that they show in their bodies,
toward the latest cutting-edge technology,
that is also particularly striking to me
It is understood that the 2018 Minhang Youth Science
and Technology Festival will organize 20 activities
By carrying out a variety of forms,
a series of unique science and technology activities
to create a good ecological environment for science and technology
innovation education in the region
We will continue to enhance young people's innovation literacy and ability,
and foster a scientific spirit and a culture of innovation
Every year, the youth Science and Technology Festival
is striving to innovate,
achieve rich content and diversified forms,
and has become a science and technology event for
the majority of young people in Minhang to share and exchange growth