They have dreams
But no platform for dreams
They are full of blood
But they don't know how to be sensual
Shy of expression
After 140 days of fighting
Countless overthrows start over
They are full of thorns
Break through themselves
Strive for excellence
Only to present their dreams perfectly
Now they have emerged from their cocoons
Harvest and joy filled their faces
Confidence and certainty are engraved in their hearts
They are the young entrepreneurs of the new era
Today they
In ways we never expected
Standing in front of us
Show their unique style
Hello, everybody
I'm Li Yunzhe from Xinzhuang Senior High School
I'm Yuan Zheng from Xinzhuang Senior High School
Hello,
I'm He Xinlin from Xinzhuang Senior High School
Hi,
I'm Yan Chenqi from Shangbao Middle School
Hello everyone,
I'm Wang Haoquan from Experimental West School
We are Hammar Master
Our project is a multi-functional hammer
A versatile new feature for the hammer
Can increase the portability of the hammer
Adjustability and replaceability
Make consumers more convenient
Our business philosophy is that innovation changes the world